{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"ABCs of Cyber Security  September Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Go Back to School with our Security Quiz.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"1. True or False: When you first sign up for an Instagram account, your profile is set to “Private”, meaning that only the followers you approve can see what you share, including your photos and videos. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: False  Unless you are under 16 when you set it up, your Instagram account is public, meaning your profile and posts can be seen by anyone, on or off Instagram, even if they don’t have an Instagram account. If you choose to set your account to private, however, only the followers you approve can see what you share. Twitter is another example of a social media platform with a default public account, while Facebook’s default is a more private “Friends Only” account. Best Practice suggests you confirm your account settings periodically.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect - Answer: False  Unless you are under 16 when you set it up, your Instagram account is public, meaning your profile and posts can be seen by anyone, on or off Instagram, even if they don’t have an Instagram account. If you choose to set your account to private, however, only the followers you approve can see what you share. Twitter is another example of a social media platform with a default public account, while Facebook’s default is a more private “Friends Only” account. Best Practice suggests you confirm your account settings periodically.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22301","si22316","si22327","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. True or False: When you first sign up for an Instagram account, your profile is set to “Private”, meaning that only the followers you approve can see what you share, including your photos and videos.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si26198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_838","roles":{}},{"id":"si26095","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_795","title":"2. Which of the following age groups is more likely to have experienced some form of online harassment? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_826","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_827","title":"18 - 29 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26106_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_435","roles":{"answer":{"title":"18 - 29\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_828","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_829","title":"30 - 49 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26117_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_436","roles":{"answer":{"title":"30 - 49\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_830","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_831","title":"50+ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26128_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"437","roles":{"answer":{"title":"50+\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_837","roles":{}},{"id":"si26220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_137","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_138","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_139","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_140","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26350","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26374","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_834","title":"Correct  - Answer: A  According to studies, roughly two-thirds of adults under 30 (64%) have experienced some form of online harassment activities.   It is important when using social media to learn how to block unwanted contact with harassing individuals. Once you block someone, they will no longer be able to interact with you. Most social media platforms also offer a means to report individuals who are engaging in harassing or threatening behaviour. You can also visit https://www.bullyingcanada.ca/get-help/ if need help.  Source: https://www.pewresearch.org/internet/2021/01/13/ the-state-of-online-harassment/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_835","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A  According to studies, roughly two-thirds of adults under 30 (64%) have experienced some form of online harassment activities.   It is important when using social media to learn how to block unwanted contact with harassing individuals. Once you block someone, they will no longer be able to interact with you. Most social media platforms also offer a means to report individuals who are engaging in harassing or threatening behaviour. You can also visit https://www.bullyingcanada.ca/get-help/ if need help.  Source: https://www.pewresearch.org/internet/2021/01/13/ the-state-of-online-harassment/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_836","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26387","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26095","si26110","si26121","si26132","si26220","si26238","si26260","si26278","si26290","si26302","si26314","si26326","si26338","si26350","si26362","si26374","si26186"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26387"},"question":{"interactionId":"26081","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. Which of the following age groups is more likely to have experienced some form of online harassment?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"3. You’re vacationing with family in Maui. You just took a fun picture with your 8-year-old niece on the beach and you want to share it on Instagram. What are some points you should consider BEFORE you decide to post it?  SELECT ALL THAT APPLY:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"Did you have geotagging enabled on your camera when you took the picture? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22905q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"Do you have a secure connection to login and upload the photo? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22905q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27528","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27532","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Have you ok’d posting this picture with your niece’s parents? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27532","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22905q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si27528_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Have you ok’d posting this picture with your niece’s parents?\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27547","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Will you tag your niece in the photo? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27547","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22905q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si27543_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct  -  Answers: A,B,C,D  All of the above points are things you should consider BEFORE you post on social media. Best practices would be to a) wait until you are home to post vacation snaps b) use a secured connection for any activities requiring a login, and confirm with the parents of minors before c) posting their photos or d) tagging (i.e. identifying) them on social media.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answers: A,B,C,D  All of the above points are things you should consider BEFORE you post on social media. Best practices would be to a) wait until you are home to post vacation snaps b) use a secured connection for any activities requiring a login, and confirm with the parents of minors before c) posting their photos or d) tagging (i.e. identifying) them on social media.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22624","si22639","si22650","si27532","si27547","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. You’re vacationing with family in Maui. You just took a fun picture with your 8-year-old niece on the beach and you want to share it on Instagram. What are some points you should consider BEFORE you decide to post it?\r\rSELECT ALL THAT APPLY:\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si26864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_864","roles":{}},{"id":"si26761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_801","title":"4. What is the best way to stay safe while using an unsecured or public Wi-Fi connection? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_852","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_853","title":"Conduct your business and disconnect from Wi-Fi as quickly as you can. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26772_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Conduct your business and disconnect from Wi-Fi as quickly as you can.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_854","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26787","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_855","title":"Use the strongest possible login passwords for any sites you plan on visiting. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26783_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use the strongest possible login passwords for any sites you plan on visiting.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_856","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_857","title":"Use a virtual private network (VPN) client. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26794_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a virtual private network (VPN) client.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_858","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26809","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_859","title":"Make sure your anti-virus program is up to date. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26805_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Make sure your anti-virus program is up to date.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_863","roles":{}},{"id":"si26886","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_145","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26904","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_146","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_147","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26944","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_148","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26980","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26992","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27004","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_860","title":"Correct  - Answer: C  Malicious users in an unsecured wireless connection can use what is called a packet sniffer to intercept and analyze any unsecured traffic. While using strong passwords and updating your anti-virus software are good security practices in general, they won’t protect against packet sniffers.  Using a VPN to encrypt your connection is the best protection as it makes any of your internet packets that malicious users intercept useless. Ultimately, however, the best way to stay safe when using the internet in public is to avoid unsecured connections/networks entirely.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26840","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_861","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: C  Malicious users in an unsecured wireless connection can use what is called a packet sniffer to intercept and analyze any unsecured traffic. While using strong passwords and updating your anti-virus software are good security practices in general, they won’t protect against packet sniffers.  Using a VPN to encrypt your connection is the best protection as it makes any of your internet packets that malicious users intercept useless. Ultimately, however, the best way to stay safe when using the internet in public is to avoid unsecured connections/networks entirely.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_862","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27053","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26761","si26776","si26787","si26798","si26809","si26886","si26904","si26926","si26944","si26956","si26968","si26980","si26992","si27004","si27016","si27028","si27040","si26852"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27053"},"question":{"interactionId":"26747","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. What is the best way to stay safe while using an unsecured or public Wi-Fi connection?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si27197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_877","roles":{}},{"id":"si27094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"5. What are some ways that a cybercriminal could steal your password or other personal/sensitive information on a public computer (e.g. computer lab, library, internet café, etc)? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_865","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_866","title":"Connecting a physical keystroke logging device (keylogger) between the keyboard and the computer. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27105_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"457","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Connecting a physical keystroke logging device (keylogger) between the keyboard and the computer.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_867","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_868","title":"Installing keylogger malware on an improperly protected public computer. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27116_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"459","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Installing keylogger malware on an improperly protected public computer.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_869","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_870","title":"Changing the homepage to a fake network login screen. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27127_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"461","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Changing the homepage to a fake network login screen.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_871","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_872","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27138_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"463","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_876","roles":{}},{"id":"si27219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_149","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_150","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_151","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_152","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27313","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27325","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_873","title":"Correct  -  Answer: D  Put simply, banking, purchases, and logging into sensitive systems (e.g. work or government accounts) should never be done on a public computer. Previously installed keyloggers could intercept your information, or malicious users may have compromised other pages or systems on the computer.   If you MUST use a public computer for schoolwork, etc, make sure there is some type of Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) software, which protects against malware and intrusion, and verify there are no suspicious devices plugged in between the keyboard and the computer.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_874","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  Put simply, banking, purchases, and logging into sensitive systems (e.g. work or government accounts) should never be done on a public computer. Previously installed keyloggers could intercept your information, or malicious users may have compromised other pages or systems on the computer.   If you MUST use a public computer for schoolwork, etc, make sure there is some type of Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) software, which protects against malware and intrusion, and verify there are no suspicious devices plugged in between the keyboard and the computer.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_875","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27386","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si27094","si27109","si27120","si27131","si27142","si27219","si27237","si27259","si27277","si27289","si27301","si27313","si27325","si27337","si27349","si27361","si27373","si27185"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27386"},"question":{"interactionId":"27080","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. What is “malvertising”?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6. True or False: Iris scanning (identifying people based on unique patterns within the ring-shaped region surrounding the pupil of the eye) is the most secure way to lock your smartphone. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct  - Answer: False  While a promising technology, at present (Aug, 2021) iris scanners can still be tricked with a high-quality image of the user’s iris with a contact lens placed over top. The most secure method of locking your smartphone continues to be a long PIN, but a complex pattern is also a good choice.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: False  While a promising technology, at present (Aug, 2021) iris scanners can still be tricked with a high-quality image of the user’s iris with a contact lens placed over top. The most secure method of locking your smartphone continues to be a long PIN, but a complex pattern is also a good choice.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6. True or False: Iris scanning (identifying people based on unique patterns within the ring-shaped region surrounding the pupil of the eye) is the most secure way to lock your smartphone.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7. Taken from a 2019 study, what percentage of data breach victims said their breaches could have been avoided by ensuring all their software was up to date (patched)? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"23% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"23%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"39% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"39%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"51% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"51%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"60% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"60%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct  -  Answer: D  According to the Ponemon Institute. 60% of breach victims said they were breached due to a know vulnerability that was left unpatched. As malicious users regularly scan for and exploit known weaknesses in systems, is essential to apply all updates as soon as possible to prevent intrusion.   Source: https://www.servicenow.com/lpayr/ponemon-vulnerability-survey.html  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  According to the Ponemon Institute. 60% of breach victims said they were breached due to a know vulnerability that was left unpatched. As malicious users regularly scan for and exploit known weaknesses in systems, is essential to apply all updates as soon as possible to prevent intrusion.   Source: https://www.servicenow.com/lpayr/ponemon-vulnerability-survey.html  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. Taken from a 2019 study, what percentage of data breach victims said their breaches could have been avoided by ensuring all their software was up to date (patched)?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si25607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","roles":{}},{"id":"si25493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_794","title":"8. Which of these options is NOT a secure way to back up your information, photos and media from your phone? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25508","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"An encrypted hard drive kept in your house ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"An encrypted hard drive kept in your house\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","title":"A regular USB drive that you keep with you on your keychain ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25515_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A regular USB drive that you keep with you on your keychain\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27582","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A reputable cloud-based storage system like Google Drive or OneDrive ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27582_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A reputable cloud-based storage system like Google Drive or OneDrive\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27597","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27601","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A password-locked computer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27597_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A password-locked computer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","roles":{}},{"id":"si25629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25699","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25747","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25771","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25571","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"Correct  -  Answer: B  An unencrypted USB drive is not a secure backup option. While it may store your data, anybody who gets their hands on it will be able to access the contents.  For backing up data, experts recommend the 3-2-1 Rule. Three (3) copies of your data in total, two (2) onsite (the original copy on your main device, with a secure backup on another device), and one (1) backup offsite, either in the cloud or on yet another secured device.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: B  An unencrypted USB drive is not a secure backup option. While it may store your data, anybody who gets their hands on it will be able to access the contents.  For backing up data, experts recommend the 3-2-1 Rule. Three (3) copies of your data in total, two (2) onsite (the original copy on your main device, with a secure backup on another device), and one (1) backup offsite, either in the cloud or on yet another secured device.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25595","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25796","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si25493","si25508","si25519","si27586","si27601","si25629","si25647","si25669","si25687","si25699","si25711","si25723","si25735","si25747","si25759","si25771","si25783","si25595"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25796"},"question":{"interactionId":"25473","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. Which of these options is NOT a secure way to back up your information, photos and media from your phone?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si27503","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27499","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" Your Correct Answers: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Sept2021Quiz","class":"project","title":"Sept2021Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide22582","Slide26387","Slide22905","Slide27053","Slide27386","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide25796","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide22582q0","Slide26387q1","Slide22905q2","Slide27053q3","Slide27386q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide25796q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide26387","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide27053","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide27386","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25796","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}